(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-13T01:46:35.098427",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
なんであなたにはできないの なんてさ
"Why can't you do it?" they say,
陰口言われたりあきれられたり 口角下がるDAY BY DAY
Badmouthed, exasperating others, the corners of my mouth drop day by day.
電車は私を置き去りにしちゃうし
The train leaves me behind,
葉物野菜もスピード早すぎだね
and leafy green vegetables spoil way too fast.
ありのままの素敵さだけじゃ足りないんだ
Just being wonderful as I am isn't enough.
毎日死ぬほど頑張ってやっとここまで連れてきたんだ
Working hard to death every day, I finally brought myself here.
あなたには分からない
You wouldn't understand.
分かって欲しくない
I don't want you to understand.
私の苦労も
Neither my struggles
このもどかしさもご存知ないでいてね
nor my frustrations—please remain unaware.
きっとあなたにもできるはず なんてさ
"I'm sure you can do it too," they say,
言うほど無責任にはなりたくない
but I don't want to be as irresponsible as those words.
それでも死ぬほど頑張って賭ける値打ちはあると思った
Even so, I thought it was worth giving my all to bet on it.
投げ出したくなるよ
I feel like giving up,
でも諦めたくはない
but I don't want to surrender.
私の未来も
My future,
失敗も全部私だけのもの
and my failures too, are all mine alone.
あなたには分からない
You wouldn't understand.
分かって欲しくない
I don't want you to understand.
私の苦労も
Neither my struggles
このもどかしさもご存知ないで
nor my frustrations, without knowing any of it—
投げ出したくなるよ
I feel like giving up.
でも諦めたくはない
But I don't want to surrender.
私の未来も
My future,
失敗も全部渡さないよ
and my failures too, I won't hand any of them over.
気づかない 気づかないでいて かわいいだけの私でいい
Don't notice, please stay unaware—just let me be the "cute" me.
アイスみたいにとろけて
Melting like ice cream,
分からなくなる
I start to lose track.
夢も愛もギュッとしていっぱいだから文字切れない
With dreams and love packed tight, I can't cut down the text,
でも欲張りすぎてきっと散っていく
but if I get too greedy, it will surely scatter away.
もうラキラキチュチュ恋に落ちちゃって
Oh, lucky lucky kiss-kiss, I've fallen in love,
キュッキュッ戻れない
squeeze-squeeze, there's no going back.
あれあれなんで？ふわりと心がまだ熱くなるの
Huh? Why is my heart softly growing hot again?
ラキラキチュチュ
Lucky lucky kiss-kiss,
君の重力で引き寄せられて
drawn in by your gravity.
カレイドスコープ覗いてるみたいで
It's like looking through a kaleidoscope.
ねえ　キラキラな未来？　見たい？　分からない
Hey, a sparkling future? Do you want to see it? I don't know.
あーアップアンドダウンで調子狂わせる
Ah, up and down, throwing me off balance.
要はね今日はね四六時中
The point is, today, 24/7,
カレンダー30日じゃ足りない
30 days on a calendar isn't enough.
あれもこれもそれも全部したい
I want to do this, that, and everything!
キュンキュンキュ上昇　ドキドキ発散
Thump-thump rising, releasing excitement!
キュンキュンキュ降下　深呼吸
Thump-thump dropping, take a deep breath.
キュンキュンキュ上昇　ラブラブメーター
Thump-thump rising, love-love meter!
キュンキュンキュ降下　電撃的ドーン！
Thump-thump dropping, electrifying BOOM!
無限大の愛抱くの　失敗だけど諦めない
Embracing infinite love, a failure but I won't give up.
まだ欲張りだから君と落ちていく
Still greedy, so I'll keep falling with you.
もうラキラキチュチュ心がハマって
Oh, lucky lucky kiss-kiss, my heart is hooked,
抜け出せない
I can't escape.
あれあれなんで？目まぐるしい心がまだ熱くなるの
Huh? Why is my dizzying heart still growing hot?
ラキラキチュチュ
Lucky lucky kiss-kiss,
スピード重視で引き寄せられて
drawn in with a focus on speed.
カレイドスコープ覗いてるみたいで
It's like looking through a kaleidoscope.
ねえ　キラキラな未来？　見たい？　分からない
Hey, a sparkling future? Do you want to see it? I don't know.
バーチャル　リアル　どっち可愛い？
Virtual or real, which is cute?
バーチャル　リアル　どっちも可愛い！
Virtual or real, both are cute!
チュッチュチュッチュチュッチュチュチュッ
Chu-chu-chu-chu...
チュリチュリチュッチュイーツイート
Churi-churi-chu Tweet!
チュッチュチュッチュチュッチュチュチュッ
Chu-chu-chu-chu...
チュリチュリチュッチュイーツイート
Churi-churi-chu Tweet!
サムネタップ初めまして　キュンキュンってしたならハート押して
Tapped the thumbnail, nice to meet you; if you felt a flutter, press the heart.
通知はオン
Turn notifications on!
いつでもウェルカム　一緒に踊ろうよ
Always welcome, let's dance together!
おーねーがーい！
Pleeaase!
お菓子食べたいけどダイエット中
I want to eat sweets, but I'm on a diet.
君の好みにアップロード中　ポチッと更新
Uploading to match your taste, updating with a click.
君と更新　もっと教えて欲しいな
Updating with you, I want you to teach me more.
バーチャル　リアル〠どっちが好き？
Virtual or real, which do you like?
つながる1・2・3次元
Connecting 1, 2, 3 dimensions,
1・2・3で飛び越えて
leap across on 1, 2, 3!
今やネットもリアルです　チクチクしないで
Now the internet is real too, don't be prickly.
ラブとピースで　ちゅっ！
With love and peace, mwah!
ときめいちゃう　ときめかせたい
My heart flutters, I want to make yours flutter too!
通知達するブブブは　混ざれば最強バーチャリアル！
When the buzz-buzz-buzz of incoming notifications mix, it's the ultimate Virtua-Real!
チュッチュチュッチュチュッチュチュチュッ
Chu-chu-chu-chu...
チュリチュリチュッチュイーツイート
Churi-churi-chu Tweet!
2番にスワイプして
Swipe to verse 2,
拡散して
spread the word!
キュンキュンってしたなら手叩いて　バズっていーよ
If you felt a flutter, clap your hands; feel free to go viral.
炎上はいーもん！
Flames are totally fine!
一緒に踊ろうよ
Let's dance together!
あーなんか界隈一だけどコラボ中
Ah, somehow #1 in the scene, but in a collab!
超楽しいことリサーチ中
Researching super fun things!
ピピピテレパシー　今日も配信
Pi-pi-pi telepathy, streaming today too!
もっとハマってほしいな
I want you to get even more hooked!
ねえねえ　どっち可愛い？
Hey, hey, which is cute?
どっち可愛い？
Which is cute?
どっちも可愛い！
Both are cute!
お菓子食べたいけどダイエット中
I want to eat sweets, but I'm on a diet.
君の好みにアップロード中　ポチッと更新
Uploading to match your taste, updating with a click.
君と更新　もっと教えて欲しいな
Updating with you, I want you to teach me more.
バーチャル　リアル　どっちが好き？
Virtual or real, which do you like?
バーチャル　リアル　どっちも好き！
Virtual or real, I like both!
一つ 二つ 三次元
One, two, three dimensions
1 2 3で飛び越えて
Leaping over on one, two, three
イライラネットも盛り上がるで
Getting excited even on the irritating internet
チクチクしないで ラブとピースで
Don't prick each other, with love and peace
チク・タク・わ・わ・わ
Tick-tock, wa-wa-wa
ときめくちょっとのきっかけが
A little spark of excitement
つながりだす 3D WORLD
Starts connecting in a 3D WORLD
まぜれば最強 ヴァーチャリアル
Mixed together, it's the strongest virtua-real
Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Jelly Chu Chu Chu
Yeah!
僕らが見ている太陽は
The sun we are looking at
8分前の景色で
Is a scene from 8 minutes ago,
実はちょっと昔らしい
And seems to actually be from a little while past.
そう考えると不思議かもね
Thinking about it that way, it's quite mysterious.
そこにあるようでいて
It seems to be right there,
少しずれた時間を過ごしてる
Yet we live in a time slightly out of sync.
きっと僕らの交差点
Surely at our intersection,
隣の人のことを
Though we don't know a single thing
ひとつも知らないけど
About the person next to us,
分かんないまま東へ向かった
Without knowing, we headed east.
天照 照らすこの手で
Amaterasu, with these illuminating hands,
触れて輪になって踊りましょう
Let's touch, form a circle, and dance.
天照 照らす気がして
Amaterasu, I feel like shining,
あのね 君だって歌えるよ
You know, even you can sing along.
誰になって降り注いだ
Pours down, whoever it reaches,
8分前の光が射す方へ
Towards where the light from 8 minutes ago shines.
僕らは分かり合えない
We cannot fully understand each other,
お互いの世界には 誰も価値をつけられない
And no one can place a value on each other's world.
それでも隣で生きてたい
Even so, I want to live by your side,
こんなに狭い星だから
Because on a planet this small,
肩でも組んでさ 歌いましょう
Let's put our arms around each other and sing.
ずっとひとりぼっちはもう最後
Being all alone forever ends here.
岩のように厚い雲を
Clouds as thick as rock,
こっそりと覗いた手を握って
I hold the hand quietly peeking through,
つかんで引っ張り出して
Grab it, and pull it out.
天照 照らす光は
Amaterasu, the illuminating light
寂しい記憶も同じように
Will illuminate lonely memories just the same,
余さず照らし出すから
Without leaving anything behind,
背中向けないで進むだけ
So just keep moving forward without turning away.
天照 照らすこの手で
Amaterasu, with these illuminating hands,
触れて輪になって踊りましょう
Let's touch, form a circle, and dance.
天照 照らす気がして
Amaterasu, I feel like shining,
あのね 君だって歌えるよ
You know, even you can sing along.
世界中のこんな朝も
Even mornings like this all over the world
8分前の光に満ちている
Are filled with light from 8 minutes ago.
ドキドキ 返事はいいけど
Heart pounding, an answer is fine, but
冗談なら笑えないよ
If it's a joke, I can't laugh about it.
渋滞 曖昧 どちらを向いちゃうの
Congested, ambiguous, which way are you turning?
蜃気楼に手を伸ばした
Reaching out toward a mirage,
微熱のような
Like a slight fever,
夢物語
A fairytale dream,
そんな光は見ないふりしてた
I pretended not to see such light.
ざわめく鼓動を
My stirring heartbeat,
まだ行かないでと
Asking "don't go yet",
惑わされちゃいたいよ
I want to be enchanted by it.
私を奪って
Sweep me away!
魅惑の Dance Dance Dance Night 広がって収まらない Universe
Entrancing Dance Dance Dance Night, an expanding, unstoppable Universe
君の意図は
Your intention
私の知る場所を
Is filled with force enough
掻き回すほどの威勢に満ちていて
To stir up the places I know.
Dazzling, marvelous day
Come on 1, 2, 3, 4! 1, 2, 3, 4!
声は闇に溶けたまま
With my voice still melted into the darkness,
目を覚ましても離れないで
even if you wake up, please don't leave me.
Maybe に心酔
Infatuated with a "maybe",
正気じゃないのよ
I'm not in my right mind.
太陽が忘れられない
I can't forget the sun.
Dull, colorless
そんなんじゃないから
it's nothing like that,
独り占めして Euphoria
so monopolize this euphoria.
気にしてないような
Act like I don't care,
言葉は装飾で
my words are just decoration,
メイクのようには流せない
I can't wash them away like makeup.
360度
360 degrees,
偽りだって隠し切れるような
as if I could completely hide even falsehoods.
私にかまって
Pay attention to me,
お焦らしで Crazy, crazy love
teasing with crazy, crazy love.
待て 廊下から連れ去る Flare
Wait, a flare taking me away from the hallway.
君の衝動は
Your impulse
私の深層心理を
turns my deep psychology upside down,
すり替えちゃうような不真面目さで
with such insincerity as to replace it.
過ぎ去った neon sign 焦燥散らかして
Passing neon signs, scattering impatience...
ゆらゆらみたいに漂えば
If I sway and drift along,
こうもこうもなかった
it wouldn't have come to this.
指先でまた 君を探している
With my fingertips, I'm searching for you again.
その声を聴かせてよ
Let me hear your voice.
私にかまって
Pay attention to me!
教えてよ恋の先を
Tell me what lies beyond love,
広がっていく散漫な夜
in this distraction expanding across the night.
君の存在は 私の将来までも
Your existence reaches even into my future,
飛び込んだ夜 惹き寄せて
pulling me in as I plunge into the night.
一切合彩 Dance, dance, dance!
Everything, all of it, dance, dance, dance!
魅惑的 Take me! 夢中になって
Enchanting, take me! Becoming crazy about you...
Dazzling, marvelous day!
Come on 1, 2, 3, 4! 1, 2, 3, 4!
声は闇に溶けたまま
With my voice still melted into the darkness,
目を覚ましても離れないで
even if you wake up, please don't leave me.
ここに宣言します
I hereby declare:
Step up, step high, step move...
息やめるときも
Whether breathing my last,
健やかなるときも
or in times of health,
ずっと
forever...
愛を歌い続けることを
that I will continue to sing of love,
堂々と誓います
I proudly vow.
歌とダンスがどうとか
Whether it's about singing or dancing,
ダンスももっと追求します
I will pursue dance even further.
いつずっと推してもらえる
To become an idol
アイドルになってみせます
whom you will support forever.
弱気な未来も
Even a timid future,
私が見照らすんだ
I will light it up!
それでも
Even so,
落ち込んじゃう日は
on days when I feel down,
思い出しているよ
I will remember...
未完成の地図を
Turning this unfinished map...
輝きに変えて
...into pure brilliance,
誰にも真似できない
watch the footsteps...
足跡を見てて
...that no one else can imitate.
みんなー！
Everyone!
走り出した願いは 加速していくスピード
Wishes that took off, accelerating in speed,
目に映るものに 戸惑うのなら
if you're bewildered by what you see,
仮想世界だって
even in a virtual world,
私が見えてるでしょう
you can still see me, right?
君だけに広がる世界が正解
The world expanding just for you is the right answer.
時々は泣き出したくもなるよ
Sometimes I feel like crying too,
だけどドキドキが プレッシャーにも勝つよ
but the thrill inside overcomes the pressure!
これから
From now on...
大きくなって 勝って
Growing bigger, winning through,
君に届けたいよ
I want to reach you.
笑顔になって 勝って
Smiling brightly, winning through,
未来も見に行こうよ
let's go see the future together!
明けない夜なんて
There's no night that never ends...
光のダイヤモンドしゃららって
A diamond of light going sha-la-la,
元気だよ 一緒に笑いたいから
I'm full of energy, because I want to laugh together!
きれいになって 勝って
Becoming beautiful, winning through,
ちょっぴり自信持って
gaining a little bit of confidence,
手から手繋いで 願って
hand in hand, making a wish,
ここで歌いたいの
I want to sing right here!
いつもよりもちょっと
A little louder than usual,
大きな声でもっと
with an even stronger voice,
かすれちゃっても
even if my voice goes hoarse,
勝手じゃないよね
that's not selfish, is it?
スポットライトもうちょっと
Shine the spotlight a little more,
当てて聴いて最高潮
listen as we reach the ultimate peak!
不安も全部巻き込んで
Embracing all the uncertainty,
上がるステージで
on this rising stage,
星の様に輝いて
shining just like a star,
これが私の役割
this is my role to play.
君だけに見せたい答えの
The world of answers...
世界
...I want to show only to you!
みんな声出していくよ！
Everyone, let's hear your voices!
せーの！
Ready, go!
どれだけ泣いても 一緒に泣いてもいいよ
No matter how much you cry, it's okay if we cry together.
だけど明日からは 明るいと確信して
But starting tomorrow, be confident that it will be bright!
大きく歌って 歌って 君に届けたいよ
Singing loud, singing out, I want my voice to reach you!
笑顔になって なって 未来を見に行こうよ
Put on a smile, a smile, and let me see the future together!
夢のない部屋を抜けて
Stepping out of this dreamless room,
風が吹く 追い風になって
the wind blows, becoming a tailwind
私達を色付ける
that adds color to us,
スポットライトだから
because it's our spotlight.
綺麗になって なって ちょっぴり自信持って
Looking pretty, so pretty, gain a little confidence!
照れちゃダメだって いいよ
It's okay, don't be shy!
君と一緒に歌いたいんだよ
I want to sing together with you!
いつまでも どこまでも 大声で
Forever and anywhere, with a loud voice,
大好きなあなたに 魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a spell on you, whom I love so much!
さあ！
Come on!
せーの！もっと！もっと！
One, two, go! More! More!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
トントン スイッチを押すと またまたすぐになれる
Knock knock, press the switch and I can transform instantly again.
ポンポン テンション高く 倒してしまうの
Bounce bounce, with high energy, taking control!
潜む視線 ハッキリシルエット 見え隠れしたその表情
Hidden gazes, a clear silhouette, that flickering facial expression.
ううん 孤独に慣れた 悪い 悪い子
Nah, a bad, bad child accustomed to solitude.
捕まえ
Catch you!
ゆらゆら揺れる 心の合図
Swaying and swinging signal of the heart.
くるくる回れ ぐるぐる回れ
Spin round and round, turn round and round.
あっち向いてホイ
Look over there!
君と遊びたいんだ 泣き虫な夜が包み込む前に
I want to play with you before the tearful night encloses us.
今夜も遊びたいんだ 寂しがりやの不器用な君は
I want to play tonight too; you lonely, clumsy person...
どんな感じ？
How are you feeling?
どっちでしょうか？ 恋しくさせてる
Which one is it? Making me miss you...
みんなを邪魔したいかな？
Do you want to interrupt everyone?
君には容赦しない
I won't go easy on you!
もう朝？
Is it morning already?
いない いない ばぁって
Playing peek-a-boo!
また また 遊びましょう
Let's play again and again.
本気で狙うよ
I'm aiming for real!
瞳の奥
Deep in your eyes,
見て て て て て て
look, look, look!
会いたいな 痛いくらいなよ
I want to see you so much it hurts.
そっと隠したのは 感情
What was quietly hidden was emotion.
どうしようかな どうしよう
What should I do? What to do?
胸が痛いよ
My chest hurts so much.
夜が明ける
Day breaks.
踊るのが好きな 私の世界に落っこちて
Fall into my world, where I love to dance!
不思議になっていくんだよ
It becomes mysterious.
ひと目で好きになりたいんだろ
You want to fall in love at first sight, don't you?
君とみた景色 描きたいんだろ
You want to draw the scenery seen with you, right?
迷い込んだ
Wandering in...
私
Me...
なんだろうよ
What could it be?
それだけ知ってる
I know just that much.
夢中になれるね
We can get absorbed in it!
個性合わせ 踊りましょう
Let me dance along with your unique self.
いらない真実(ほんとう)は 忘れさせてあげたいから
I'll make you forget the truths you don't need,
上手の駆け引きに
so in this clever bargaining,
そっぽ向いたら
if you turn away...
イェイ イェイ イェイ イェイ
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
あー
Ah~
ひと目で好きになりたいんだろ
You want to fall in love at first sight, don't you?
君とみた景色 描きたいんだろ
You want to paint the scenery seen with you, right?
迷い込んだ
Wandering in...
私
Me...
なんだろうよ
What is it?
どっちでしょうか？
Which one is it?
本気にしてる
Taking it seriously,
素直になっちゃいそうだから
because I feel like becoming honest with myself.
君には容赦しない
I won't go easy on you!
心躍る
My heart leaps!
痛いのもまた
Even the pain is...
あはっ
Aha!
ドキドキ隠せないけど
I can't hide my pounding heart,
冗談なら笑えないよ
but if it's a joke, it's not funny.
痛快 曖昧 どっちが勝者なの
Thrilling or ambiguous, who's the winner?
蜃気楼に手を伸ばした
I reached out toward a mirage
迷宮の夜に
into the labyrinthine night.
おとぎ話の魔法だったり 存在感みたいに信じてた
I believed in it like fairytale magic or a true presence.
ちょっと待って この目を
Wait a minute, look at my eyes...
まだ行かないで まぼろしじゃないよ
Don't go yet, this isn't an illusion.
私に構って
Pay attention to me!
今すぐ焦燥感脱ぎ捨てて
Cast off this impatience right now.
広がっていく 散漫なユニバース
A scattered universe continues to expand.
君の都合は
Your circumstances...
私の知らない場所の 鍵が邪魔して 無責任みたいで
are locked away somewhere I don't know, feeling so irresponsible.
探して 探して 探しても
Searching, searching, no matter how much I search,
あたしを映すレイニー
the rain reflects my image.
散々絡み合った
Intricately intertwined
からから道
down a dry, empty path.
散々散っちゃったって
Even if it all falls completely apart,
恋は傷ついたまんま
love remains wounded.
目を覚ましても 離れないで
Even if I wake up, please don't leave me.
レイジーに逃げ出しそうだよ
I feel like lazily running away.
太陽が眩しくなる夜
On a night where the sun grows dazzlingly bright,
理由なんて言えないから
because I can't even give a reason.
一人イメージして 降りや
Imagining it all alone...
気にしてないようね
You don't seem to care at all.
鈍感なポーズして 迷宮の夜には逃げ出せない
Posing as oblivious, I can't escape this labyrinthine night.
ちょっと待って この手を
Wait a minute, holding this hand...
どこへ連れて行くつもりだって
Where do you intend to take me?
寂しくなるよ
I'll get lonely.
私に構って
Pay attention to me!
新鮮なプレゼンスを
Give me a fresh presence.
螺旋を描くフレア 散らして
Scattering a spiraling flare...
君の都合は
Your circumstances...
私の深層心理を
touch my deep subconscious,
限界じゃないよ 責任散らして
this isn't my limit, casting off responsibility,
過ぎ去ったネオン残像処理して
processing the afterimages of neon that passed by.
グライダーみたいに漂えば
If I float like a glider,
今日も恐怖もなかった
there was no fear today either.
行き先でまた 君を探している
At my destination, I'm searching for you again.
その声を聞かせてよ
Let me hear your voice!
私に構って
Pay attention to me!
惜しみなく恋の先を
Unsparingly, beyond this love...
広がっていく 散漫なユニバース
A scattered universe continues to expand.
居場所は
Where I belong...
私の将来までの
Even fragments leading to my future...
欠片だって妄想に酔いしれて
I'm intoxicated by delusional fantasies.
探して 探して 探しても
Searching, searching, no matter how much I search,
あたしを映すレイニー
the rain reflects my image.
散々絡み合った
Intricately intertwined
からから道
down a dry, empty path.
散々散っちゃったって
Even if it all falls completely apart,
恋は傷ついたまんま
love remains wounded.
目を覚ましても 離れないで
Even if I wake up, please don't leave me.
イェーイ！
Yay!
皆さん 新年あけましておめでとうございます！
Everyone, Happy New Year!
はーい！盛り上がってますかー？
Alright! Is everyone having a great time?
みんなで協力して 優しい気持ちでライブできてるかにゃ？
Is everyone working together and enjoying the concert with kind hearts?
いいねー！素晴らしいよー！
That's great! Wonderful!
みんな見えてるよー 今日はみんな青いんだね。そっか あれか あのTシャツ
I can see everyone! Everyone's glowing blue today. Ah, right, that T-shirt!
Tシャツが 今着てくれてる人？
Who's wearing the T-shirt right now?
はーい！
Yay!
待って、当日券買ってくれた人って現場にいますか？
Wait, is there anyone here who bought a same-day ticket?
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
すごい！感動した！ありがとうございます！本当に嬉しいです！
Amazing! I'm so touched! Thank you so much, I'm really happy!
ということで、ね！やりました。あれをやろうか！
So, with that... yes! We did it. Shall we do that thing?
そうですね、遠くから来てくれた人ー！
Let's see... Anyone who came from far away?
ねー、飛行機とかで来てくれた人いたもんね！
Right, there were people who came by plane and everything!
じゃあ、海外アニキ！
Next, overseas bros!
じゃあ、声は出さなくてもいい、あのクルクルやるだけでもいいよ、女の子！
Next, you don't even have to shout, just waving your penlights is fine too... Girls!
きゃー！ありがとう！
Kyaa! Thank you!
前のほうでぴょんぴょん跳んでるの、見えたよー！めちゃくちゃ爆笑してる！
I saw you hopping up and down in the front! You're laughing so hard!
奥のほうの子も見えてるよー！大声ありがとうございます！
I can see the ones in the back too! Thank you for shouting so loud!
そして… 2階席ー！
And... second balcony!
1階席ー！
First balcony!
じゃあまたペンライト変えちゃおう
Alright, let's change our penlight colors again!
左の人、緑！
People on the left, green!
右の人はじゃあ、オレンジ！
People on the right, let's go with orange!
じゃあ、真ん中は… 青ー！
And in the middle... blue!
うわー、綺麗だー！
Woah, so pretty!
みんな、今回はね、こんな感じで
Everyone, this time around,
みんなも演出に参加しちゃうライブになっているよ
it's a live concert where you all get to participate in the production!
みんなで楽しんでいこうねー！
Let's all have fun together!
今日はみんなも主役なんだー！
Today, all of you are the main stars too!
おいしい、おいしい… おいしいから！
It's so good... It tastes good!
夜はね、いっぱい動くと思って… 昼から飲めばよかった
I knew I'd be moving around a lot tonight... I should've started drinking this since noon.
スポドリ一択！
Sports drinks are the only way to go!
がっつり… 今年はムキムキになっていこうと思います！
I'm planning to work hard... and build some real muscle this year!
というわけで…
So with that said...
じゃーん！ 初めての人ー！
Ta-da! Is anyone here for the first time?
あっ、拍手してくれてありがとうございます！
Ah, thank you so much for applauding!
一番最初のライブから全部来てるよって人いる？
Is there anyone here who's been to every single concert since the very first one?
おおー！ ありがとうございます！
Oh, wow! Thank you so much!
というわけでね、初めましての人も
So, you see? Whether you're here for the first time,
いつもは来られない人も、昔から応援してる人も
or you can't usually make it, or you've been supporting me for a long time,
みんな集まって、みんなが全そらともだよ！
everyone gathered here, you're all true Soratomo!
みんな楽しく過ごしていこうねー！
Let's all have a wonderful time together!
というわけで…
And so...
なんと… YouTubeでの無料配信…
Believe it or not... the free broadcast on YouTube...
まだ何も言ってないのにー！
I haven't even said anything yet!
まだ来たばかりかと思いますけど…
I know you feel like you just got here...
続きは概要欄から…
but you can catch the rest from the description box...
「イエーイ」の人はどうしたの？
What's with the people cheering "Yeah!"?
配信会場の人も楽しんでいってねー！
Everyone watching the stream, enjoy the rest of the show too!
それでは、もう一回飲んでから行くね。水分も大事！
Well then, I'll take another drink before we move on. Hydration is important!
「助かる」って言ってくれてありがとう！
Thank you for saying "Bless you"!
では、次の曲も楽しんでいってね！
Now then, please enjoy the next song too!
まだほんのちょっと
Still just a little bit
未完成な私
of an incomplete me
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
[The free preview broadcast ends here.]
The free preview stream ends here.